let questions = [{
    title: 'part1',
    questionNumber: 1,
    questionBody: 'What year did the Russian Revolution start?',
    answers: ['1905', '1939', '1917', '1919'],
    correctAnswer: '1917'
  },
  {
    title: 'part2',
    questionNumber: 2,
    questionBody: 'Who is regarded as the leader of the revolution?',
    answers: ['Lenin', 'Stalin', 'Trotsky', 'Churchill'],
    correctAnswer: 'Lenin'
  },
  {
    title: 'part3',
    questionNumber: 3,
    questionBody: 'In which country was Lenin in exile?',
    answers: ['Switzerland', 'Belgium', 'Luxembourg', 'Uruguay'],
    correctAnswer: 'Switzerland'
  },
  {
    title: 'part4',
    questionNumber: 4,
    questionBody: 'Which faction won the Russian Civil war?',
    answers: ['The Whites', 'Bolsheviks', 'Mensheviks', 'Anarchists'],
    correctAnswer: 'Bolsheviks'
  },
  {
    title: 'part5',
    questionNumber: 5,
    questionBody: 'What tools were on the Soviet flag?',
    answers: ['Hammer and Sickle', 'Spade and Rake', 'Trowel and Hoe', 'Tractor and Bakkie'],
    correctAnswer: 'Hammer and Sickle'
  },
  {
    title: 'part6',
    questionNumber: 6,
    questionBody: 'The mutiny of which ship  is viewed as leading to the revolution?',
    answers: ['Dreadnought', 'Enterprise', 'Kursk', 'Potemkin'],
    correctAnswer: 'Potemkin'
  },
  {
    title: 'part7',
    questionNumber: 7,
    questionBody: 'In which what year did this mutiny take place?',
    answers: ['1905', '1939', '1917', '1919'],
    correctAnswer: '1905'
  },
  {
    title: 'part8',
    questionNumber: 8,
    questionBody: 'During which war did the revolution take place?',
    answers: ['First World War', 'Second World War', 'Napoleonic Wars', 'Korean War'],
    correctAnswer: 'First World War'
  },
  {
    title: 'part9',
    questionNumber: 9,
    questionBody: 'What did USSR stand for?',
    answers: ['Union of Slavic Socialist Republics', 'United Supreme Socialists Rave', 'United States of South Russia', 'Union of Soviet Socialist Republics'],
    correctAnswer: 'Union of Soviet Socialist Republics'
  },
  {
    title: 'part10',
    questionNumber: 10,
    questionBody: 'By what name were the revolutionary forces known?',
    answers: ['Pink Army', 'Red Army', 'White Army', 'People\'s Liberation Army'],
    correctAnswer: 'Red Army'
  },
  {
    title: 'part11',
    questionNumber: 11,
    questionBody: 'Which Tsar was executed during the revolution?',
    answers: ['Peter the Great', 'Catherine', 'Nicholas II', 'Ivan'],
    correctAnswer: 'Nicholas II'
  },
  {
    title: 'part12',
    questionNumber: 12,
    questionBody: 'What was the name of the famous mystic who was reputed to be nigh unkillable?',
    answers: ['Rasmussen', 'Raslenin', 'Rastalin', 'Rasputin'],
    correctAnswer: 'Rasputin'
  },
  {
    title: 'part13',
    questionNumber: 13,
    questionBody: 'Who ended up as the leader of the USSR?',
    answers: ['Lenin', 'Stalin', 'Trotsky', 'Churchill'],
    correctAnswer: 'Stalin'
  },
  {
    title: 'part14',
    questionNumber: 14,
    questionBody: 'Which of these Nations did not aid the White Army?',
    answers: ['British Empire', 'Japanese Empire', 'USA', 'Germany'],
    correctAnswer: 'Germany'
  },
  {
    title: 'part15',
    questionNumber: 15,
    questionBody: 'What was the pejorative name given to wealthy peasants during the revolution?',
    answers: ['Kulaks', 'Streloks', 'Cheeki Breeki', 'Katyusha'],
    correctAnswer: 'Kulaks'
  },
  {
    title: 'part16',
    questionNumber: 16,
    questionBody: 'How many revolutions were in the Russian Revolution?',
    answers: ['One', 'Two', 'Three', 'Four'],
    correctAnswer: 'Two'
  },
  {
    title: 'part17',
    questionNumber: 17,
    questionBody: 'What was the city of Petrograd renamed to?',
    answers: ['Leningrad', 'Stalingrad', 'Kiev', 'Minsk'],
    correctAnswer: 'Leningrad'
  },
  {
    title: 'part18',
    questionNumber: 18,
    questionBody: 'Which member of the royal family was it rumoured had escaped?',
    answers: ['Anastasia', 'Alexandra', 'Alexei', 'Maria'],
    correctAnswer: 'Anastasia'
  },
  {
    title: 'part19',
    questionNumber: 19,
    questionBody: 'In which year did the USSR dissolve?',
    answers: ['1991', '1990', '1989', 'Still secretly running'],
    correctAnswer: '1991'
  },
  {
    title: 'part20',
    questionNumber: 20,
    questionBody: 'Which famous allegorical novel was written about the Russian Revolution?',
    answers: ['1984', 'Charlotte\'s Web', 'Animal Farm', 'A Brave New World'],
    correctAnswer: 'Animal Farm'
  }

]
let messages = [
  "How!?",
  "Nearly there",
  "Nice!"
]
